Stephen Hunt

Frisco, Texas, United States

thestephenhunt@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/thestephenhunt

Summary

I work on the front end of an onboarding form to bring in new clients. I have 10+ years of professional experience in web development, UI engineering, and software engineering, across various domains and technologies.

Previously, I was a senior frontend developer at Peapod Digital Labs. I worked with Vue to add a new feature for same day delivery. I also collaborated as a leader for an internal development education initiative and built a Slack bot to integrate multiple sources of documentation. I am passionate about creating quality products, solving problems, and learning new skills.

Experience

Senior Frontend Developer

Peapod Digital Labs

Nov 2023 - Present (7 months)

Software Engineer II

Bank of America

Apr 2023 - Sep 2023 (6 months)

- Worked on a onboarding form to bring in new clients
- Worked with an in-house framework built around Vue

SUser Interface Engineer

Nurocor, Inc

Feb 2020 - Jan 2023 (3 years)

- Completed a UI redesign on our oldest current product, replacing an old component library with a new one, and writing new components
- All products were built with the Nuxt.js framework
- Built the UI of a platform-wide notification service
- Built and updated components within our custom component library using Storybook
- Began a transition to Typescript and Vue 3 across our platform
- Wrote tests using Vue-Test-Utils and Jest
- Did some prototyping with TailwindCSS for future components

ul Engineer II

Cox Automotive Inc.

Jun 2018 - Feb 2020 (1 year 9 months)

- Created new feature for determining which cars on a dealer's lot are hot or not utilizing React, AWS, and Java
- Refactored tracking system for new internal framework based on React using Javascript
- Maintained and added to the Ford specific design variation utilizing SCSS

- Collaborated as a leader for an internal development education initiative
- Built a Slack bot on free time to bring together multiple sources of documentation

Web Developer

DIRECTV Latin America

May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

- Built out the front-end redesign for DirecTV's Latin American site leveraging HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular 5 and PHP
- Set up base installation and built components for a website utilizing Angular 5
- Built a small informational website with Kirby CMS
- Created a custom style guide leveraged internally using Bootstrap
- Collaborated directly with a designer to convert PSDs to websites
- Developed all projects listed above to be responsive

Web Developer

Inked Brands

Sep 2016 - Apr 2017 (8 months)

- Leveraged HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, Git, and Bash on the front-end
- Created view templates for new features on their custom-built platform (Ruby on Rails) that enhanced and improved the user experience
- 90% of SCSS maintained affected the entire platform, shared across multiple sites
- Turned designs from the UX/UI team into responsive pages
- Initiated the platform-wide conversion to from jQuery to JavaScript
- Responsible for bug fixes and implementing improvements on the platform, which increased functionality and usability on mobile platforms

Web Developer

PartnerComm, Inc.

Aug 2014 - Sep 2016 (2 years 2 months)

- Leveraged HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, and Git on all projects
- Leveraged PHP and MySQL for WordPress projects, and C# and MySQL on different projects with the .NET team
- Coded all projects to be compatible with IE8+ browsers
- Served primarily as a Front-End Developer
- Collaborated with back-end engineers on both WordPress and C# platforms, and bridged the gap between design and function
- Committed changes to an in-house custom theme with a custom framework, which resulted in more concise and mobile friendly code
- Created several sites from scratch based on the platform, and was responsible for site maintenance for those projects

Lead QA Tester

Hitcents

Aug 2013 - Jul 2014 (1 year)

I got my feet wet in C# development and testing.

Operations Manager

Nintendosforsale.com

Apr 2010 - Jul 2013 (3 years 4 months)

My hands touched every aspect of business here, from inventory management, to purchasing and customer service!

Education

Florida College

Graphic Design 2006 - 2008

Self taught

Web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Wordpress

Skills

ESLint • Written Communication • Semantic HTML • English • Agile Methodologies • GraphQL • Communication • Handlebars.js • PHP • JavaScript